let's talk about friends do you have
lots of friends I do have quite a few
friends um I I feel like I have more
acquaintances than friends the people
who I really care about I think I can
definitely count them on my fingers who
is your best friend and why I don't know
how to answer this question because if I
say any one person the others are going
to come after me and also I don't have
just one best friend I
have maybe three or four very very good
friends who I Look to for help
counseling
advice and uh I treasure them I I really
appreciate each and every one of them
for different reasons are you the type
of person that makes friends easily it's
really interesting because in a new
environment I can be rather closed off
I've had people tell me actually you're
very nice you know once they get to know
me but I kind
of am a bit more of ANS ever not that I
um not that I'm not willing to socialize
with people but I kind of like to sus
out my environment before I say anything
in case I offend anybody now let's talk
about flowers have you ever given
anybody flowers I give people flowers uh
all the time I think it's really lovely
to receive a bouquet of flowers what's
funny is that I'm not such a not that
I'm not a big fan of receiving flowers
but I'm not really bothered about
receiving flowers is it popular to give
Flowers in Your Country yes but I think
we have to avoid white flowers because
they use white flowers at funerals I'm
not sure if I'm guting this right but I
think there are certain colors that we
need to avoid what kind of flowers do
you like to receive I don't like cliches
so I don't like red roses I love
sunflowers I like daisies anything
that's bright and happy and cheerful and
not particularly extravagant or out
there now let's talk about food do you
enjoy cooking oh I love cooking I have
tried to improve my cooking skills
during the past year or two I would say
it was successful so I've uh tried my
hand at kishes and uh Thai food I love
Thai food I love the flavors the
turmeric and the lemongrass it's very I
think distinctive oh I've tried baking
as well I still cannot get my uh whipped
cream to stiffen uh it melts a bit but
we'll see let's see how we can fix that
what are the most popular dishes in your
country in Taiwan we love to promote our
stinky tofu it smells absolutely
horrendous but people tend to like
stinky tofu they prefer the fried
version to the I don't know if they boil
it but they prefer it fried they say it
tastes uh it tastes best but I can't get
over the smell other things we do really
well bubble tea came from tywan that's a
huge Trend around the world and um we
have our own version of uh Fried Chicken
which I really love it's very good let's
talk about noise are you comfortable
with loud noises no in general no
construction sites are understandable
angry shouting people not so
understandable so
I think it depends if it's a
construction site next to your office
and you have to be at the office I can
tolerate it but if it's someone just
being a bit extra then
maybe we'll skip that what type of
noises do you come across during your
daily routine types of noises everyday
noises I think a lots of the noises that
we hear every day are quite uh can be
quite familiar and homey such as the
toaster going off or an egg sizzling in
a pan they're quite random but they can
be quite like I said comforting describe
a tourist attraction that you would
recommend so I highly recommend CM rev
um it's these beautifully preserved
temples in the middle of the Cambodian
jungle and it is a UNESCO heritage site
but apart from that one of the temples
also appeared in uh Tomb Raider it's the
Tomb Raider film with Angelina Jolie cuz
I know that they got another actress to
fill that role um recently actually
you'll remember there's a scene where
she's in a temple and there's a Buddha
head that's kind of
like buried in in a tree trunk people
tend to remember that Temple for that
reason and so they go to visit this
Temple when they're in cm RAB um in
general I love Cambodia it was the first
trip that I felt really connected to
prior to that I'd been to Europe and I
was in Paris um Luxembourg Spain I did
this whole trip because I was um on
Exchange uh Europe is beautiful Europe
is very beautiful but I felt a special
connection with Cambodian and I would
definitely go back so apart from cmre I
would recommend panon pen as well but
definitely if you if you have to go to
Cambodia you cannot miss cmre there's
this eerily beautiful Vibe or energy
about the place that I really enjoy it's
very peaceful and very quiet so we've
been talking about a tourist attraction
that you would recommend let's continue
to talk about museums and art galleries
and the holiday industry do you believe
that all museums and art galleries
should be free to thank you for watching
this video I want to give you a free
course that has helped thousands of
students improve their I speaking score
what it's going to do is take you
through every single part of the test
and give you strategies for part one
part two and part three and also allow
you to practice at home for free and get
feedback to sign up for that for free
all you have to do is just click the
link in the description thanks very much
and let's get back to the video so I
would say my first instinct is to say
that yes I believe that art galleries
museums should be free because what's
inside them all the artifacts and his
historical paintings and books and
whatnot they belong to the people they
belong to the human race however I also
understand that upkeep is expensive um
maintenance is also very costly so I
think maybe charging a small
fee um is is very reasonable I I like
what they've done in in France
especially uh because they allow people
to go to museums for free every first
Sunday I believe of the month something
like that what kind of things make a
museum or Art Gallery an interesting
place to visit I would say it would
depend really on the pass in because
what I find interesting might not be
very interesting for somebody else what
I find interesting I would say mostly uh
I like Salvatore Del and um Renee mcgr
so I like a lot of serialist
painters if we're talking about art but
I also do enjoy oh I I really like the
national is it the British history
museum yeah in London that one was
really nice now let's talk about the
holiday industry why do you think some
people book package holidays rather than
traveling
independently thank you for making it
this far in the video I want to give you
10% off our VIP course I VIP course is
the most successful I course in the
world that is a fact because we have
more band seven eight and N success
stories than any other ILS course in the
entire world we do that by simplifying
the whole ILS process supporting you
with some of the best is teachers in the
world and being with you every step of
the way until you get the score that you
need all you have to do is just look
down in the description just click that
and you can sign up if you have any
questions about the VIP course always
feel free to get in touch with us we
answer 100% of the questions that we get
hope that you become a VIP if not enjoy
the rest of this free video I think some
people do so because they don't really
like the planning aspect of it perhaps
I'm someone who really enjoys traveling
independently the only time I did travel
with a group was when we went to Egypt
because there are some tourist
attractions um that you cannot access if
you're not with a tour guide that was
the only time uh we ever traveled with a
group of people perhaps I think senior
citizens they might enjoy traveling in a
group it would make things more
interesting as well are there any
negative impacts of large numbers of
tourists visiting an area when I used to
live in Paris I felt the negative
impacts quite intensely there's a lot
more traffic
um there's a lot
more how would I put
it Hubb lots of crowds it's very chaotic
it can get very messy people are
shouting but I think in general the pros
outweigh the cons because for countries
such as France they depend strongly on
tourism for a large part of the of the
country's income the GDP so
I don't
know I like
Taurus for the most part why not that's
the end of the speaking test well done
thank you